Guide to the Red Hot Organization Archive, 1989-2004 MSS.191
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series III: No Alternative, 1993
  - Subseries C: Photographic Material
    - Photograph: Pavement, [n.d.]; cuid7394 (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Photograph: Smashing Pumpkins, 1993; cuid7395 (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - Photograph: Sonic Youth, 1992; cuid7396 (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - Photograph: Soul Asylum, 1993; cuid7397 (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - Photograph: Soundgarden, 1992; cuid7398 (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - Photograph: Straitjacket Fits, [n.d.]; cuid7399 (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - Photograph: Sweet, Matthew, 1993; cuid7400 (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - Photograph: Urge Overkill, 1993; cuid7401 (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - Photograph: The Verlaines, [n.d.]; cuid7402 (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - Slides (color): Album covers, [n.d.]; cuid7403 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Subseries D: Merchandise
    - No Alternative, 1993; cuid7404 (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - No Alternative CD sleeves autographed by Billy Corgan, James Iha and D'arcy of The Smashing Pumpkins, 1993; cuid7405 (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - No Alternative sampler, 1993 - 1994; cuid7406 (Box 5, Folder 31)
- Series IV: Red Hot + Publish, [n.d.]
  Red Hot + Publish contains publishing tools including Mac and Windows versions of QuarkXTensions and Photoshop plug-ins.
  - Subseries D: Merchandise
    - Postcards: "I LOVE YOU!" Designed by Mary M. Hauck, 1993; cuid7407 (Box 5, Folder 32)
    - Postcard: Designed by Anne Russinof, 1993; cuid7408 (Box 5, Folder 33)
    - Postcards: Designed by Daniel Will-Harris, 1993; cuid7409 (Box 5, Folder 34)
    - Postcard: Designed by Donald G. Biglands, 1993; cuid7410 (Box 5, Folder 35)
    - Postcards: Designed by Ina Saltz, 1993; cuid7411 (Box 5, Folder 36)
    - Postcards: Designed by Ina Saltz and Joe Lertola, 1993; cuid7412 (Box 5, Folder 37)
    - Postcards: Designed by Jean Foos, 1993; cuid7413 (Box 5, Folder 38)
    - Postcards: Designed by Jim Feld, 1993; cuid7414 (Box 5, Folder 39)
    - Postcards: Designed by Lax Syntax Design, 1993; cuid7415 (Box 5, Folder 40)
    - Postcards: Designed by Lorraine and Johnny Mak, 1993; cuid7416 (Box 5, Folder 41)
    - Postcards: Designed by Luisa Simone and Robbin Juris, 1993; cuid7417 (Box 5, Folder 42)
    - Postcards: Designed by Margery Peters, 1993; cuid7418 (Box 5, Folder 43)
    - Postcards: Designed by Marina Brolin, 1993; cuid7419 (Box 5, Folder 44)
    - Postcards: Designed by Marlitt Dellabough, 1993; cuid7420 (Box 5, Folder 45)
    - Postcards: Designed by new chi zone design, 1993; cuid7421 (Box 5, Folder 46)
    - Postcards: Designed by Paul Davis / In memory of Peter Hallock, 1993; cuid7422 (Box 5, Folder 47)
    - Postcards: Designed by Paul Davis / In memory of Tony Papp, 1993; cuid7423 (Box 5, Folder 48)
    - Postcards: Designed by Pauline Ores, 1993; cuid7424 (Box 5, Folder 49)
    - Postcards: Designed by Tom Lulevitch, 1993; cuid7425 (Box 5, Folder 50)
    - Postcard: Illustrated by Marlene Sezni, 1993; cuid7426 (Box 5, Folder 51)
    - Red Hot + Publish; Quark, Inc. etc., 1993; cuid7427 (Box 5, Folder 52)
      Diskette
    - Red Hot + Publish, Set 1, [n.d.]; cuid7428 (Box 5, Folder 53)
    - Red Hot + Publish, Set 2, [n.d.]; cuid7429 (Box 5, Folder 54)
- Series V: Red Hot + Country, 1994
  Red Hot + Country was released in 1994 by Mercury Nashville, featuring classic country and rock songs performed by old and new country artists. The album received two Grammy nominations. An accompanying home video was released by PolyGram Video. (Reference: http://www.redhot.org)
  - Subseries A: Production Files
    - "Close Up The Honky Tonks", 1993; cuid7430 (Box 5, Folder 55)
    - "Fire And Rain", 1993-1995; cuid7431 (Box 5, Folder 56)
    - "Forever Young", 1993; cuid7432 (Box 5, Folder 57)
    - "Keep On The Sunnyside", 1994; cuid7433 (Box 5, Folder 58)
    - "Pictures Don't Lie", 1994; cuid7434 (Box 5, Folder 59)
    - "Teach Your Children", 1993; cuid7435 (Box 5, Folder 60)
    - "Willie Short", 1994; cuid7436 (Box 5, Folder 61)
    - Active, [n.d.]; cuid7437 (Box 5, Folder 62)
    - Advances from PolyGram Records, Inc. (video label), 1994; cuid7438 (Box 5, Folder 63)
    - Audio tracking log, [n.d.]; cuid7439 (Box 5, Folder 64)
    - Bogguss, Suzy, 1994-1995; cuid7440 (Box 5, Folder 65)
    - Brooks & Dunn, 1993-1994; cuid7441 (Box 5, Folder 66)
    - Browne, Jackson, 1993-1995; cuid7442 (Box 5, Folder 67)
    - Budget, 1993-1994; cuid7443 (Box 5, Folder 68)
    - Cash, Johnny, 1994; cuid7444 (Box 5, Folder 69)
    - Chestnutt, Mark, 1993-1994; cuid7445 (Box 5, Folder 70)
    - Clairol cassette single + CD info, 1993-1994; cuid7446 (Box 5, Folder 71)
    - Clearances - Labels, 1995; cuid7447 (Box 5, Folder 72)
    - Clearances - Publishing, 1993-1994; cuid7448 (Box 5, Folder 73)
    - Contact list, [n.d.]; cuid7449 (Box 5, Folder 74)
    - Crowell, Rodney, 1995; cuid7450 (Box 5, Folder 75)
    - Disk, 1994; cuid7451 (Box 5, Folder 76)
      SyQuest 44 MB 5.25" Removable Cartridge
      Removable Hard Drive moved to Series XXIV: Organizational Digital Data Storage.
    - Eddy, Duane, cuid7452 (Box 5, Folder 77)
    - Gilmore, Jimmy Dale, 1994; cuid7453 (Box 5, Folder 78)
    - Griffith, Nanci, 1993-1994; cuid7454 (Box 5, Folder 79)
    - Hoffman, Rand, 1993-1994; cuid7455 (Box 5, Folder 80)
    - Kershaw, Sammy, 1994; cuid7456 (Box 5, Folder 81)
    - Liberty Records, 1994; cuid7457 (Box 5, Folder 82)
    - Licensing, 1993-1995; cuid7458 (Box 5, Folder 83)
    - Licensing, 1994-1995; cuid7459 (Box 5, Folder 84)
    - Licensing - Clairol cassette single, 1993-1994; cuid7460 (Box 5, Folder 85)
    - Loveless, Patty, 1994; cuid7461 (Box 5, Folder 86)
    - Mattea, Kathy, 1992; cuid7462 (Box 5, Folder 87)
    - Nelson, Willie, 1994; cuid7463 (Box 5, Folder 88)
    - Ono Lennon, Yoko, 1993; cuid7464 (Box 5, Folder 89)
    - Other labels, 1994; cuid7465 (Box 5, Folder 90)
    - Painting waivers, 1994; cuid7466 (Box 5, Folder 91)
    - Parton, Dolly, 1994; cuid7467 (Box 5, Folder 92)
    - Perkins, Carl, 1993-1994; cuid7468 (Box 5, Folder 93)
    - Recording budget and expenses, 1993-1994; cuid7469 (Box 5, Folder 94)
    - Royalties audit - Contracts, 1999; cuid7470 (Box 5, Folder 95)
    - Royalty statement, 1995; cuid7471 (Box 5, Folder 96)
    - Ryman Auditorium event - Crew all access pass, 1995; cuid7472 (Box 5, Folder 97)
    - Ryman Auditorium event - VIP pass, 1995; cuid7473 (Box 5, Folder 98)
    - Sales breakdown, 1995-1997; cuid7474 (Box 5, Folder 99)
    - The Scruggs, 1994-1995; cuid7475 (Box 5, Folder 100)
    - Signed contracts, 1993-1994; cuid7476 (Box 5, Folder 101)
    - Signed synchronization licenses, 1994-1995; cuid7477 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Stuart, Marty, 1994; cuid7478 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Sullivan, Jerry and Tammy, 1994-1995; cuid7479 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - TV show, 1993-1994; cuid7480 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Video synchronization rights, 1994-1995; cuid7481 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Video tracking log, c.a. 1995; cuid7482 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - VIDEO WAIVERS (Restricted), 1994-1995; cuid7483 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Watson, Doc, 1994; cuid7484 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Wilco, [n.d.]; cuid7485 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Subseries B: Promotional Material
    - Address re: ribbon controversy, [n.d.]; cuid7486 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Clairol cassette single, 1993; cuid7487 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Clairol cassingles, 1994; cuid7488 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Decals - Red Hot + Country, [n.d.]; cuid7489 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Information packet master, c.a. 1993; cuid7490 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Media guidelines for participating artists, [n.d.]; cuid7491 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Pamphlets - Red Hot + Country, [n.d.]; cuid7492 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Press clippings, 1992-1995; cuid7493 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Press clippings, 1994; cuid7494 (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - Press clippings, 1994; cuid7495 (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - Press release, 1992; cuid7496 (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - Red Hot + Country; Mercury Nashville (Promotional), 1994; cuid7497 (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - Red ribbon badge - Red Hot + Country, [n.d.]; cuid7498 (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - Table tents - Red Hot + Country, [n.d.]; cuid7499 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Subseries C: Photographic Material
    - Photograph: Stuart, Marty, [n.d.]; cuid7501 (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - Photographs: Recording artists, [n.d.]; cuid7502 (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - Slides (color): Live show at Ryman Auditorium - Rodney Crowell, Waylon Jennings, Nanci Griffith, Kathy Mattea, Mark Collie, Radney Foster, John Hiatt, [n.d.]; cuid7503 (Box 6, Folder 26)
    - Slides (color): Live show at Ryman Auditorium - Duane Eddy, Carl Perkins, [n.d.]; cuid7504 (Box 6, Folder 27)
    - Slides (color): Live show at Ryman Auditorium - mostly crew, John Carlin, Randy Scruggs, cuid7505 (Box 6, Folder 28)
    - Slides (color): Live show at Ryman Auditorium - Crew, Levon Helm, Radney Foster, [n.d.]; cuid7506 (Box 6, Folder 29)
    - Slides (color): Live show at Ryman Auditorium - Mark Collie, Earl Scruggs, [n.d.]; cuid7507 (Box 6, Folder 30)
    - Slides (color): Live show at Ryman Auditorium - Sammy Kershaw, Kathy Mattea, [n.d.]; cuid7508 (Box 6, Folder 31)
    - Slides (color): Live show at Ryman Auditorium - Earl Scruggs, Billy Ray Cyrus, Levon Helm, crew, [n.d.]; cuid7509 (Box 6, Folder 32)
    - Slides (color): Live show at Ryman Auditorium - Jimmie Dale Gilmore, Radney Foster, crew, [n.d.]; cuid7510 (Box 6, Folder 33)
    - Slides (color): Live show at Ryman Auditorium - Carl Perkins, [n.d.]; cuid7511 (Box 6, Folder 34)
    - Slides (color): Live show at Ryman Auditorium - Duane Eddy, Carl Perkins, The Mavericks, Shelby Lynne, Billy Ray Cyrus, [n.d.]; cuid7512 (Box 6, Folder 35)
    - Slides (color): Live show at Ryman Auditorium - All, [n.d.]; cuid7513 (Box 6, Folder 36)
    - Slides (color): Live show at Ryman Auditorium - Radney Foster, Levon Helm, Rodney Crowell, Nanci Griffith, crew, [n.d.]; cuid7514 (Box 6, Folder 37)
    - Slides (color): Live show at Ryman Auditorium - Randy Scruggs, Billy Ray Cyrus, cuid7515 (Box 6, Folder 38)
    - Slides (color): Live show at Ryman Auditorium - Crew, John Carlin, Jimmie Dale Gilmore, [n.d.]; cuid7516 (Box 6, Folder 39)
    - Slides (color): Live show at Ryman Auditorium - Crew, Jimmie Dale Gilmore, Radney Foster, Carl Perkins, [n.d.]; cuid7517 (Box 6, Folder 40)
    - Slides (color): Live show at Ryman Auditorium - John Carlin, crew, [n.d.]; cuid7518 (Box 6, Folder 41)
    - Slides (color): Live show at Ryman Auditorium, most credited to Theresa Montgomery and Jed Dekalb, 1995; cuid7519 (Box 6, Folder 42)
    - Slides: Recording artists, [n.d.]; cuid7520 (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - Subseries D: Merchandise
    - Red Hot + Country; Mercury Nashville, 1994; cuid7521 (Box 6, Folder 44)
    - Red Hot + Country; Mercury Nashville, 1994; cuid7522 (Box 6, Folder 45)
    - Red Hot + Country; Mercury Nashville (tire packaging), 1994; cuid7523 (Box 6, Folder 46)
    - Red Hot + Country; PolyGram Video, 1995; cuid7524 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Red Hot + Country CD inserts (partial), 1994; cuid7525 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Series VI: Stolen Moments: Red Hot + Cool, 1994
  Stolen Moments: Red Hot + Cool was released by GRP Records in 1994, featuring collaborations between jazz performers and hip hop artists. A documentary film focusing on the impact of AIDS on communities of color was broadcast on PBS in tandem with the album release, and released on home video by PolyGram Video. (Reference: http://www.redhot.org)
  - Subseries A: Production Files
    - Advances from ITVS and GRP Records (label), 1994 - 1995; cuid7526 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Advertising, 1994; cuid7527 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Approval memos, 1994; cuid7528 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Audio tracking log, 1994 - 1997; cuid7529 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Axium Productions, Inc. (Restricted), 1994; cuid7530 (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Bank account, 1994 - 1995; cuid7531 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Billing - Artwork (Restricted), 1994 - 1995; cuid7532 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Billing - Paid, 1994 - 1995; cuid7533 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Billing - Receipts (Restricted), 1994 - 1995; cuid7534 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Billing - Sent (not paid), 1995; cuid7535 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Budget, 1993 - 1994; cuid7536 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Budgets and information for independents, 1994; cuid7537 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Byrd, Donald / Guru (Restricted), 1993 - 1994; cuid7538 (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - Carter, Ron, 1994; cuid7539 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Cherry, Don, 1994; cuid7540 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Coltrane, Alice, 1993 - 1994; cuid7541 (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence - Hot 97 FM, 1994; cuid7542 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Digable Planets (Restricted), 1993 - 1994; cuid7543 (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - Film production cost summary, [n.d.]; cuid7544 (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - Film production files (Restricted), 1994; cuid7545 (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - Franti, Michael, 1994; cuid7546 (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - Groove Collective, 1994; cuid7547 (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - GRP, [n.d.]; cuid7548 (Box 7, Folder 25)
      Maxell 1.44 MB disk
    - Hancock, Herbie, 1994; cuid7549 (Box 7, Folder 26)
    - Incognito, 1994; cuid7550 (Box 7, Folder 27)
    - ITVS (Independent Television Service, Inc.), 1993 - 1994; cuid7551 (Box 7, Folder 28)
    - The Last Poets (Restricted), 1993 - 1994; cuid7552 (Box 7, Folder 29)
    - Live shoot releases (Restricted), 1994; cuid7553 (Box 7, Folder 30)
    - Marsalis, Branford, 1993 - 1994; cuid7554 (Box 7, Folder 31)
    - MC Solaar / Rakhim, 1994 - 1999; cuid7555 (Box 7, Folder 32)
    - Music videos (Restricted), 1991 - 1995; cuid7556 (Box 7, Folder 33)
    - NdegeOcello, Me'shell (Restricted), 1994; cuid7557 (Box 7, Folder 34)
    - The Pharcyde, 1994; cuid7558 (Box 7, Folder 35)
    - Publishing waivers - all tracks, 1993 - 1994; cuid7559 (Box 7, Folder 36)
    - RHO#6 Stolen Moments, 1994-1996; cuid7560 (Box 7, Folder 37)
    - The Roots (Restricted), 1994; cuid7561 (Box 7, Folder 38)
    - Rosenworld, 1994; cuid7562 (Box 7, Folder 39)
    - Royalties audit, 1996 - 1999; cuid7563 (Box 7, Folder 40)
    - Royalty statement, 1995; cuid7564 (Box 7, Folder 41)
    - Sales breakdown for foreign royalties, 1996 - 1998; cuid7565 (Box 7, Folder 42)
    - TV agreements (Restricted), 1994; cuid7566 (Box 7, Folder 43)
    - TV releases (Restricted), 1994; cuid7567 (Box 7, Folder 44)
    - Us3, 1994; cuid7568 (Box 7, Folder 45)
    - Video folder, 1994; cuid7569 (Box 7, Folder 46)
    - Video tracking log, c.a. 1995; cuid7570 (Box 7, Folder 47)
    - Watson, Wah Wah, 1994 - 1995; cuid7571 (Box 7, Folder 48)
    - Watts Prophets, 1994; cuid7572 (Box 7, Folder 49)
  - Subseries B: Promotional Material
    - Condoms - Stolen Moments: Red Hot + Cool, cuid7573 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Flier - Live at the Supper Club, 1994; cuid7574 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Fliers - Stolen Moments: Red Hot + Cool home video, [n.d.]; cuid7575 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Fliers - Stolen Moments: Red Hot + Cool track listing, 1994; cuid7576 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Information packet, [n.d.]; cuid7577 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Invitation to advance screening of Stolen Moments: Red Hot + Cool, 1994; cuid7578 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Invitations to live filmed event at Supper Club, 1994; cuid7579 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Mugs - Stolen Moments: Red Hot + Cool, [n.d.]; cuid7580 (Box 36)
      Mugs are housed in a separate box - Box 36.
    - Postcard ad - "You better stop and think about it", [1994]; cuid7581 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Postcard ads - "Time is moving on, you better get with it before it's gone.", [1994]; cuid7582 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Postcard ads - Red Hot + Cool, 1994; cuid7583 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Postcard invitations to "A Celebration of Stolen Moments: Red Hot + Cool", c.a. 1995; cuid7584 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Press clippings, 1993-1994; cuid7585 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Promotional single: "Proceed II," The Roots w/ Roy Ayers; GRP Records, 1995; cuid7586 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Red Hot On Impulse!; GRP Records (Promotional), 1994; cuid7587 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - The Red Hot Organization Presents: Live at the Supper Club, 1994; cuid7588 (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Sample: Stolen Moments: Red Hot + Cool (Japanese version); GRP Records, 1994; cuid7589 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - Stickers - Stolen Moments: Red Hot + Cool, [n.d.]; cuid7590 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Subseries C: Photographic Material
    All photographs are black and white.
    - Contact sheets: Credited to Kristine Larsen, [n.d.]; cuid7591 (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - Film negative fragments (16 mm): Beard, skyline + brick wall, [n.d.]; cuid7592 (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Film negatives and photo: SM Party, cuid7593 (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - Mock-ups: Donald Byrd; credited to Dana Lixenberg, 1994; cuid7594 (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - Mock-up: Jimmy Jay & MC Solaar; credited to Dana Lixenberg, 1994; cuid7595 (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - Mock-up: Jimmy Jay, MC Solaar & GURU; credited to Dana Lixenberg, 1994; cuid7596 (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - Mock-up: Jimmy Jay, Ron Carter & MC Solaar; credited to Dana Lixenberg, 1994; cuid7597 (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - Mock-up: Lester Bowie & The Digable Planets; credited to Dana Lixenberg, 1994; cuid7598 (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - Mock-up: Me'Shell NgedeOcello; credited to Dana Lixenberg, 1994; cuid7599 (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - Mock-up: Wah Wah Watson; credited to Dana Lixenberg, 1994; cuid7600 (Box 8, Folder 27)
    - Photographs: Beard, [n.d.]; cuid7601 (Box 8, Folder 28)
    - Photograph: Hancock, Herbie, [n.d.]; cuid7602 (Box 8, Folder 29)
    - Photographs: Marsalis, Branford; credited to Bruce Caines, 1992; cuid7603 (Box 8, Folder 30)
    - Photographs: Publicity stills of artistes, cuid7604 (Box 38)
    - Preservation negatives: Skyline + beard, [n.d.]; cuid7605 (Box 8, Folder 31)
    - Slides: Mostly for Red Hot on Impulse, [n.d.]; cuid7606 (Box 8, Folder 32)
    - Slides: Mostly publicity stills, one credited to Guy Aroch, [n.d.]; cuid7607 (Box 8, Folder 33)
    - Slides (color): Publicity stills of artistes, [n.d.]; cuid7608 (Box 8, Folder 34)
    - Slides: Publicity stills of artistes (titled "More b+w copies" but contents are not all black and white), cuid7609 (Box 8, Folder 35)
    - Photographs: GRP Publicity Shots, undated; cuid7610 (Box 24a, Folder 1)
    - Photographs: Stolen Moments Color and B & W, undated; cuid7611 (Box 24a, Folder 2)
  - Subseries D: Merchandise
    - A Little on the CD Side: Musician Magazine's New Music Sampler, Volume 16; Ivy Hill, [n.d.]; cuid7612 (Box 8, Folder 36)
    - Stolen Moments: Red Hot + Cool; GRP Records, 1994; cuid7613 (Box 8, Folder 37)
    - Stolen Moments: Red Hot & Cool; PolyGram Video, 1994; cuid7614 (Box 8, Folder 38)
    - Stolen Moments: Red Hot & Cool VHS sleeve, 1994; cuid7615 (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - Subseries E: Awards
    - Golden Gate Award, San Francisco International Film Festival, 1995; cuid7616 (Box 8, Folder 40)
    - Silver Apple Award, National Educational Media Network, 1995; cuid7617 (Box 8, Folder 41)
- Series VII: Red Hot + Bothered, 1995
  Red Hot + Bothered was initially released in 1995 as "Red Hot + Bothered Volume I Number 1" and "Red Hot + Bothered Volume I Number 1," two 10" EP's with limited edition fanzines by indie writers and artists. A full-length CD was later released in the same year, containing extra tracks not available on the vinyl EP's. (Reference: http://www.redhot.org)
  - Subseries A: Production Files
    - Advance against profits from Warner Bros. Records, 1995; cuid7618 (Box 8, Folder 42)
    - Audio tracking log, [n.d.]; cuid7619 (Box 8, Folder 43)
    - Babe the Blue Ox - "Hazmats" video, 1995; cuid7620 (Box 8, Folder 44)
    - Budget/billing, 1995; cuid7621 (Box 8, Folder 45)
    - Clearances - Signed, 1995; cuid7622 (Box 8, Folder 46)
    - Invoices - Paid, 1994 - 1995; cuid7623 (Box 8, Folder 47)
    - Invoices - Pending, 1995; cuid7624 (Box 8, Folder 48)
    - Legal information, 1995; cuid7625 (Box 8, Folder 49)
    - Marketing, 1995; cuid7626 (Box 8, Folder 50)
    - Project accounting for "Fanzine", 1995; cuid7627 (Box 8, Folder 51)
    - Publishing rights, 1994 - 1995; cuid7628 (Box 8, Folder 52)
    - RH+Bothered #2 archive, 1992-1995; cuid7629 (Box 8, Folder 53)
      Removable Hard Drive has been moved to Series XXIV: Organizational Digital Data Storage.
    - Video tracking log, [n.d.]; cuid7630 (Box 8, Folder 54)
  - Subseries B: Promotional Material
    - Flier - Red Hot + Bothered 1, [1995]; cuid7631 (Box 8, Folder 55)
    - Fliers - Red Hot + Bothered 2, [1995]; cuid7632 (Box 8, Folder 56)
    - Invitation to release of Red Hot + Bothered, 1995; cuid7633 (Box 8, Folder 57)
    - Postcard ads - Red Hot + Bothered, 1995; cuid7634 (Box 8, Folder 58)
    - Press clippings, 1995 - 1996; cuid7635 (Box 8, Folder 59)
    - Press releases, 1995; cuid7636 (Box 8, Folder 60)
    - Stickers - Red Hot + Bothered, [n.d.]; cuid7637 (Box 8, Folder 61)
    - Table tent - Red Hot + Bothered, 1995; cuid7638 (Box 8, Folder 62)
  - Subseries C: Photographic Material
    - Slides (color): Red Hot & Bothered #2 zine cover, 1995; cuid7639 (Box 8, Folder 63)
  - Subseries D: Merchandise
    - Red Hot + Bothered; Kinetic Records, 1995; cuid7640 (Box 8, Folder 64)
    - Red Hot + Bothered CD insert (back), 1995; cuid7641 (Box 8, Folder 65)
- Series VIII: The Beat Experience / Offbeat: A Red Hot Soundtrip
  This series encompasses both "The Beat Experience" CD-ROM/Video and "Offbeat: A Red Hot Soundtrip" enhanced audio CD.
  Released by WAX TRAX / TVT in 1996, "Offbeat: A Red Hot Soundtrip" was an offshoot of The Beat Experience, a project exploring the legacy of the Beat generation produced by The Red Hot Organization in association with the Whitney Museum of American Art. "The Beat Experience" CD-ROM combines text, jazz, underground films and visual art to anthologize the period, while "The Beat Experience" video is an hour TV show that presents the era in a contemporary edit of archive filmclips, sound bites, music and abstract imagery.
  (Reference: Offbeat: A Red Hot Happening flier; http://www.redhot.org)
  - Subseries A: Production Files
    - Adamson, Barry, 1995; cuid7642 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Advances from Wax Trax Records (label) and Voyager (distributor), 1995 - 1996; cuid7643 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Audio tracking log, [n.d.]; cuid7644 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Baraka, Amiri / DJ Spooky, cuid7645 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Beat Disk (contents: Budget.xls, Footage.xls, flmcred.doc & VHS list), [n.d.]; cuid7646 (Box 9, Folder 5)
      TDK micro floppy disk
    - Billing: Mastering, Editing, 1995 - 1996; cuid7647 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Budget notes, [n.d.]; cuid7648 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Budget / Paid invoices (Restricted), 1995-1996; cuid7649 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Carney, Ray, 1995; cuid7650 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Clearances, 1995 - 1997; cuid7651 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Clearances: Labels, Artists, Publish, 1995 - 1996; cuid7652 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Contracts, CD-ROM & Film: Outstanding, 1995; cuid7653 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence, 1995 - 1996; cuid7654 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Credits, 1995; cuid7655 (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Distribution, 1995 - 1997; cuid7656 (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - DJ Krush, 1995 - 1996; cuid7657 (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - Emergency Broadcast Network, 1995; cuid7658 (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - Expenses: Party/Event, 1996; cuid7659 (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - Footage (Restricted), 1995-1996; cuid7660 (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - Footage, 1995; cuid7661 (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - Laika / My Bloody Valentine, 1995 - 1996; cuid7662 (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - McBride, Christian / DJ Krazy, 1995; cuid7663 (Box 9, Folder 22)
    - Masters, 1995 - 2001; cuid7664 (Box 9, Folder 23)
    - Meat Beat Manifesto, 1995; cuid7665 (Box 9, Folder 24)
    - Music - Masters, 1993-1995; cuid7666 (Box 9, Folder 25)
    - Music - Publishers, 1995; cuid7667 (Box 9, Folder 26)
    - Music / Spoken word, [n.d.]; cuid7668 (Box 9, Folder 27)